Toggle Menu

Privacy Policy
--------------

Protecting your private information is our priority. This Statement of Privacy applies to responsability.net, and Digital Respons-Ability and governs data collection and usage. For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, unless otherwise noted, all references to Digital Respons-Ability include respons-ability.net, Digital Parenting and digitalparenting.com. The Digital Respons-Ability website is a Educational Technology site. By using the Digital Respons-Ability website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.

Collection of your Personal Information
---------------------------------------

We do not collect any personal information about you unless you voluntarily provide it to us.  
However, you may be required to provide certain personal information to us when you elect to use certain products or services. These may include: (a) registering for an account; (b) entering a sweepstakes or contest sponsored by us or one of our partners; (c) signing up for special offers from selected third parties; (d) sending us an email message; (e) submitting your credit card or other payment information when ordering and purchasing products and services. To wit, we will use your information for, but not limited to, communicating with you in relation to services and/or products you have requested from us. We also may gather additional personal or non-personal information in the future.

Sharing Information with Third Parties
--------------------------------------

Digital Respons-Ability does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties.

Digital Respons-Ability may share data with trusted partners to help perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to Digital Respons-Ability, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.

Digital Respons-Ability may disclose your personal information, without notice, if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Digital Respons-Ability or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Digital Respons-Ability; and/or (c) act under exigent  
circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Digital Respons-Ability, or the public.

Tracking User Behavior
----------------------

Digital Respons-Ability may keep track of the websites and pages our users visit within Digital  
Respons-Ability, in order to determine what Digital Respons-Ability services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within Digital Respons-Ability to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.

Automatically Collected Information
-----------------------------------

Information about your computer hardware and software may be automatically collected by Digital Respons-Ability. This information can include your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times, and referring website addresses. This information is used for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the Digital Respons-Ability website.

Security of your Personal Information
-------------------------------------

Digital Respons-Ability secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use, or  
disclosure. Digital Respons-Ability uses the following methods for this purpose:

\-SSL Protocol

When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other websites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) protocol.

We strive to take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or  
alteration of your personal information. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect  
your personal information, you acknowledge that: (a) there are security and privacy limitations  
inherent to the Internet which are beyond our control; and (b) security, integrity, and privacy of any and all information and data exchanged between you and us through this Site cannot be guaranteed.

Right to Deletion
-----------------

Subject to certain exceptions set out below, on receipt of a verifiable request from you, we will:

* Delete your personal information from our records; and
* Direct any service providers to delete your personal information from their records.

Please note that we may not be able to comply with requests to delete your personal information if it is necessary to:

* Complete the transaction for which the personal information was collected, fulfill the terms of a written warranty or product recall conducted in accordance with federal law, provide a good or service requested by you, or reasonably anticipated within the context of our ongoing business relationship with you, or otherwise perform a contract between you and us;
* Detect security incidents, protect against malicious, deceptive, fraudulent, or illegal activity; or prosecute those responsible for that activity;
* Debug to identify and repair errors that impair existing intended functionality;
* Exercise free speech, ensure the right of another consumer to exercise his or her right of free speech, or exercise another right provided for by law;
* Comply with the California Electronic Communications Privacy Act;
* Engage in public or peer-reviewed scientific, historical, or statistical research in the public interest that adheres to all other applicable ethics and privacy laws, when our deletion of the information is likely to render impossible or seriously impair the achievement of such research, provided we have obtained your informed consent;
* Enable solely internal uses that are reasonably aligned with your expectations based on your relationship with us;
* Comply with an existing legal obligation; or
* Otherwise use your personal information, internally, in a lawful manner that is compatible with the context in which you provided the information.

Children Under Thirteen
-----------------------

Digital Respons-Ability does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen. If you are under the age of thirteen, you must ask your parent or guardian for permission to use this website.

Website Disclaimer
------------------

The information provided by Digital Respons-Ability (“we”,”us,” or “our”) on our respons-ability.net (the “site”) is for general information purposes only. All information on the site is provided in good faith, however, we make no representation or warranty of any kind, express or implied, regarding the accuracy, adequacy, validity, reliability, availability, or completeness of any information on the site. UNDER NO CIRCUMSTANCES SHALL WE HAVE ANY LIABILITY TO YOU FOR ANY LOSS OR DAMAGE OF ANY KIND INCURRED AS A RESULT OF THE USE OF THE SITE OR RELIANCE ON ANY INFORMATION PROVIDED ON THE SITE. YOUR USE OF THE SITE AND YOUR RELIANCE ON ANY INFORMATION ON THE SITE IS SOLELY AT YOUR OWN RISK.

E-mail Communications
---------------------

From time to time, Digital Respons-Ability may contact you via email for the purpose of providing announcements, promotional offers, alerts, confirmations, surveys, and/or other general communication.

If you would like to stop receiving marketing or promotional communications via email from Digital Respons-Ability, you may opt-out of such communications by Clicking on the unsubscribe button.

Changes to this Statement
-------------------------

Digital Respons-Ability reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your account, by placing a prominent notice on our website, and/or by updating any privacy information. Your continued use of the website and/or Services available after such modifications will constitute your: (a) acknowledgment of the modified Privacy Policy; and (b) agreement to abide and be bound by that Policy.

Contact Information
-------------------

Digital Respons-Ability welcomes your questions or comments regarding this Statement of  
Privacy. If you believe that Digital Respons-Ability has not adhered to this Statement, please  
contact Digital Respons-Ability at:

Digital Respons-Ability  
586 N 290 E  
Vineyard, Utah 84059

Email Address:  
contact@respons-ability.net

Telephone number:  
3853130575

Effective as of November 02, 2022

###### Programs

###### Resources

###### About

© 2024 Digital Digital Respons-Ability. All Rights Reserved.

* [Programs](https://respons-ability.net/digital-citizenship-programs/)Expand child menuExpand
    
    * [For Educators](#)Expand child menuExpand
        
    * [For Students](#)Expand child menuExpand
        
    * [For Parents](#)Expand child menuExpand
        
    * [For Administrators](#)Expand child menuExpand
        
* [Resources](#)Expand child menuExpand
    
* [About DRA](https://respons-ability.net/about/)Expand child menuExpand
    
* [Trainings By State](#)Expand child menuExpand
